Hello Friends, if I tell you that at
this time when six and a half to
seven percent interest is going on from the applicant, then if someone
offers you an insurance plan,
subscribe to Great Settings, like you did
there, they appointed me,
click on subscribe, that's the
appointment, subscribe, how to
now I was told about the scheme, there it was
only a production film,
all six suppository short term insurance
plans and I heard it there and
after that I came home, I
started doing some research about it,
information given on ICC's side,
whether this plan is there and this cream is there, so
basically based on my input, they
told me about its best, they offered me an advanced
line, what does the plan say,
you will get a
guaranteed addition of ten percent on this premium per year, so for
example, if I took the first year, third, Pawan
Express, then I would get
20% of the premium on it and 1000 20, in the second year, the
asked letter will be Tubelight, so
click on its button  2004, so I will get it till 10
and on top of this, overhead tank, we are
also offered guaranteed maturity benefits
and by combining these two, the amounts are
final, they told me that in watching the film, I subscribed for a total of
five years, so a
total of only ₹5 and in return I am subscribed for 15 years, so I was
not subscribed, I would
like to tell you that this Amavasya scheme will
vary depending on your age, depending on
how many years you
want to invest, there are many schemes
offered in it in which it is said that
give money till this year, you will get the return after this,
you want this much after 10 years, if you want the
return then it goes on the road,
such different options are given to you here, so
which option do you choose, its
best option comes, but without the
calculations that we will do here, you
can see your prospective appointee, so
we subscribe and go ahead, if we had this
and this was in us, then we will take it and the
hair number that we enter here, then I will keep it from youth  I
want to know till the end of the year or
that I paid premium for 5 years and I
got a job, this
is only a premium, I take the
rate of interest as per cent per cent,
so if I
take 65 patients, then I will see that the monthly
interest is not paid for a long time
and if I
talk about relative interest then I will start adding these, so
we see that according to our calculations
and that the premium interest is
Rs. 6.5 lakhs, the same amount
he had also given in his calculations here,
apart from this he has given guaranteed
maturity benefits Tilak to him,
so I do this in the name of village MB
and I take this difficulty 2013 and
my total will come by adding these two and it will be
approximately 900.33
Now this amount which I am getting after 15 years of medical treatment, then
what is my rate of interest because
if you look at it with basic mathematics, then there is
no compounding involved in it  I have the
amount that I have given through,
I should earn some amount by compounding it, so
what will I do, I will ask another
question and then we will try to know how much
percentage of this amount that we have effectively earned,
so I will
start another calculation with this
that you will get per Prem Yagya,
if I apply interest on it according to the send button, then I will get this interest in the
first year
and my amount will be of
this country plus
subscribe, I will get that interest, I will
not get that interest only at this time,
actually I should get the interest which I had
taken in the previous year, hence I should get that also by adding it, so
I click here on Revise
Investment
that Jaitley Mahua this amount plus this arm hole,
now I will apply the government end percentage on it, what happened,
I have taken this much amount and the
amount at the end of the second year will be my revised
term and plus device interest, now
if I go for the third year, then my total amount in the third year will be of
like share  If I
apply 10% premium for the year plus this then my device will be possible
and if I lose 1500 cylinder then this mark will give
me approximate amount,
I will turn it off,
you see that the
amount and offer that I am getting is 3 CR, it should actually
come in 20%,
05 06, but I have only 98100
3330, so if you see this, this is a very big
Ghagra ns200, so the interest given here
is simple interest for you and it
remains computing, if you see then subscribe
but the appointed committee has got the rate of interest,
use a very obscene on it,
subscribe and subscribe, so
I have to change its value and enter the
value which I have for the target person and by
changing the value cell, I will enter it, so
here you can see
that I have approximately 5%
interest, if I
increase the pulse inside it to decibels, if  If I
want, then my interest of 5.15 is being received
and in this particular
line, my written and displayed in this file
is 12150 now but when you are
taking an insurance plan, then there is some other
butter with it like you get subscription plus
you get it at 10, so if you want, then let us
see what difference does it make and if
you want, that means you are
not getting any question on maturity, now
we use that subscribe button,
so quickly I will show you what is it,
if I give you 10 percent of your
amount, suppose you are taxed, I am
not charging any surcharges on it, just
for this simplicity, if we take 10 percent, then
my revised amount will be
its return percentage 90 thousand
rupees, the NAC share will also be 90,000 and this will remain
and my return revolving
investment will remain that
point, taking piece at last, now we have the same
formula  Let's see how much
our profits come. If we
apply this pattern percentage here, then we have the
approximate return of 15 lakh 67 thousand.
So, Lakshit's
net profit should come in the maximum time. If Praful is
investing this amount, you have saved Dashrath,
but looking at our positive
position, we have seen that we have got
Rs. 4.5 lakh, see the total amount we got was this much. So
if we have got the return above the pony, then
we are here
in the same form, we will go to the declaration,
I will change it, we will take 9703 and by
changing the price or face, we will do ok, this gives us a
return of 606.
If I mean, if you
are in the three percent bracket, then you get a return
of 606. If we talk about if we can do it with 20%, then
we look at it this way,
so we do it
and make a new formula. Here is the result,
this is my approximately 31 lakh.
I should have got a return of 180
but I got 19710. Now let us see
how much percentage of return we have in Red Chilli to get this rate of interest.
You will come to the office and
enter it in the voter list in the circle shape 9703 Life Changing Rewards in the end and
do it. So we have 06 of ours.
If you are able to save 20% tax at the minimum.
If you are able to save 40% of your tax, if
40% is in the centre
then you will get 7.01 more.
And now you have to see whether the play is
useful or not. I do not recommend whether
this product is good or not but
I just wanted to check that when
you are shown the carat saving sign in this
way that you are getting the notification, then
please take some time on it and
calculate. You can see that 15209
we have found out that the rate of return is
not 20% but the product is  There is an
insurance product, you are
also getting insurance with it, is the
value of that insurance sufficient now, which
you were being shown 4%, this 5% extra,
or if you
look at the rest available in the market, if there is a 2% rate of
interest, then is it
worthless or not, then take a decision
only after expressing the various possibilities,
so that whether this is a
good product for you or not, I hope this
video is helping you, if you
like this video, then please press the like button
and tell me in the comment section how
you found it useful and if
you have any other questions, then thank you
for watching and staying updated.